Guide to the Rice University KTRU Radio records, 1962-2018 UA 011
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series I: Audio recordings, 1968-2007, 59004
  - Sub-Series: 1979/1980, 59315
    - To the Point - Richard Smith, 1980-01-15; wrc06858 (Box 12)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Matt Muller talks with Dr. Richard Smith about the relationship between the U.S., Russia, and China vis-à-vis Afghanistan. Speakers: Richard Smith, Matt Muller
    - Dan Downey interview, 1980-01-21; wrc06859; 59354 (Box 12)
      Contents include: Dan Downey, running for the Texas State Legislature District 80, discusses his plans for education reform and crime reform. We deleted extraneous audio from the beginning of this recording. Speakers: Mark Linimon, Dan Downey
    - To the Point - William Howell, 1980-01-22; wrc06860 (Box 12)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Kathryn Makris talks with Dr. William Howell about his recent Houston crime study. Speakers: William Howell, Kathryn Makris
    - To the Point - Kathleen Matthews, 1980-01-28; wrc06861 (Box 12)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Matt Muller talks with Dr. Kathleen Matthews about test tube babies. Speakers: Kathleen Matthews, Matt Muller
    - To the Point - John Margrave, 1980-01-30; wrc06862 (Box 12)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Matt Muller talks with Dr. John Margrave about scientific research spending. Speakers: John Margrave, Matt Muller
    - To the Point - John Freeman, 1980-02-04; wrc06863 (Box 12)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Matt Muller talks with Dr. John Freeman about energy costs and future budgetary planning. Speakers: John Freeman, Matt Muller
    - To the Point - Frank Bearden, 1980-02-12; wrc06864 (Box 12)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Kathryn Makris talks with Dr. Frank Bearden about physical fitness in the U.S. Speakers: Frank Bearden, Kathryn Makris
    - To the Point - John Anderson, 1980-02-13; wrc06865 (Box 12)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Kathryn Makris talks with Dr. John Anderson about marine geology in Antarctica. Speakers: John Anderson, Kathryn Makris
    - State of the University, 1980-02-14; wrc06866 (Box 12)
      Contents include: The Rice Associates present Norman Hackerman giving his "State of the University" address. He discusses faculty salaries, administration, the athletic program, and energy. Secretary of the Department of Energy Charles Duncan speaks about energy use. Speakers: Norman Hackerman, Charles Duncan
    - Up in the Air - Philip Roos, 1980-02-14; wrc06867 (Box 12)
      Contents include: On "Up in the Air," Philip Roos talks about his book about how parents and professionals can care for handicapped children. We deleted extraneous audio from the beginning of this recording. Speakers: Philip Roos
    - Up in the Air - Sanford Criner, 1980-02-15; wrc06868; 59350 (Box 12)
      Contents include: On "Up in the Air," Walter Keeler and Mark Linimon interview Sanford Criner, owner of the Rockefeller's music venue. He discusses renovating the Heights State Bank building, choosing and booking talent, promotion, and dealing with musicians and managers. Speakers: Sanford Criner, Walter Keeler, Mark Linimon
    - Anti-Draft Rally at Hermann Park, 1980-02-16; wrc06869; 59343 (Box 12)
      Contents include: Speakers and singers protest President Jimmy Carter and Congress's renewal of draft registration. Because the tape was recorded at a very fast speed, we have corrected it. We also removed white noise. Speakers: Richard King, Jim Steele, Jeff Calvert
    - Up in the Air - Rev. Charles A. Moore, 1980-02-22; wrc06870; 59353 (Box 12)
      Contents include: On "Up in the Air," Rev. Charles A. Moore talks about his mission to Iran to visit with hostages and plead for their release, during the Iran hostage crisis. We deleted extraneous audio from the beginning of this recording. Speakers: Charles A. Moore, Jim Fowler, Frank Vance, David Butler
    - To the Point - Ken Kennedy, 1980-02-22; wrc06871 (Box 12)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Kathryn Makris talks with Dr. Ken Kennedy about relating to computers, their history, and future. Speakers: Ken Kennedy, Kathryn Makris
    - To the Point - Niels Nielsen, 1980-02-25; wrc06872 (Box 12)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Kathryn Makris talks with Dr. Niels Nielsen about religious studies in public schools. Speakers: Niels Nielsen, Kathryn Makris
    - To the Point - James Blackburn, 1980-03-12; wrc06873 (Box 12)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Kathryn Makris talks with James Blackburn about energy planning. Speakers: James Blackburn, Kathryn Makris
    - Christianity vs. Humanism debate (2 audio cassettes), 1980-03-14; wrc06874; 69743 (Box 12)
      Contents include: Dr. Norman Geisler and Dr. Konstantin Kolenda debate, representing Christianity and Humanism respectively. They also answer questions on the topic. Speakers: Greg Hinkle, Norman Geisler, Konstantin Kolenda
    - News Morgue, 1980-03-17-1980-04-29; wrc06895; 59330 (Box 12)
      Contents include: (00:01) Lone Star Train Route rally; (04:21) Baker College Shakespeare Festival; (08:53) Norman Hackerman announces Lovett and Jones College become co-ed; (09:58) Baker Shakespeare's Romeo and Juliet review; (12:23) Rice Players' Seascape; (14:09) New administrative appointments; (15:45) Arne Troelstra interview; (22:40) Beer Bike update; (23:47) John B. Anderson running for independent presidential candidate; (24:40) Sid Richardson College bomb; (26:20) League of Women Voters Republican debate; (30:31) Gen. David Jones on Iran hostage rescue; (30:37) John Ford of Gov. Bill Clements on Iran hostage rescue; (31:10) John Tower on Iran hostage rescue; (31:46) Sen. Ted Kennedy on Iran hostage rescue; (32:35) Lovett College chili cock-off; (33:49) Pres. Jimmy Carter on Sec. Cyrus Vance resignation; (34:40) Earl Cooper in NFL draft; (35:44) NFL draft. Speakers: David Butler, Francis Loewenheim, Al Edwards, Jim Hoffmeister, Jack Martin, Jeffrey Kurtzman, Norman Hackerman, Paul C. Graves, Mary Kay Zuravleff, Arne Troelstra, George H. W. Bush, Ronald Reagan, Bill Brey, David Jones, John Ford, John Tower, Jimmy Carter, Ted Kennedy, David Tuttle
    - To the Point - Joseph Cooper, 1980-03-24; wrc06875 (Box 12)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Kathryn Makris talks with Dr. Joseph Cooper about the relationship between the U.S. president and congress. Speakers: Joseph Cooper, Kathryn Makris
    - Arbuckle Flat - Randal Calcote, 1980-03-25; wrc06876; 59346 (Box 12)
      Contents include: Randal Calcote performs on the show "Arbuckle Flat." We have removed white noise from this recording. Speakers: Walter Keeler, Randal Calcote
    - To the Point - Robert Stein, 1980-03-26; wrc06877 (Box 12)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Steve Sailer talks with Dr. Robert Stein about federal funding for state and local governments. Speakers: Robert Stein, Steve Sailer
    - To the Point - Frank Bearden, 1980-03-28; wrc06878 (Box 12)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Mark Winstein talks with Dr. Frank Bearden about the U.S.'s boycott of the 1980 Olympics. Speakers: Frank Bearden, Mark Winstein
    - News Archive 1, 1980-04-01-1980-08-24; wrc06897; 59356 (Box 12)
      Contents include: (00:01) Jones and Lovett Colleges becoming co-ed in Fall 1980; (01:29) Sen. Edward Kennedy critiquing Pres. Jimmy Carter; (02:38) Sen. Edward Kennedy on unemployment; (03:36) George Bush for President Headquarters on Texas primary night; (05:39) Gov. Bill Clements on Texas Republican Headquarters; (06:45) Gov. Ronald Reagan on winning delegates; (07:33) Democratic chairman John White on winning in general election; (08:02) Ken Dye appointed Director of the Marching Owl Band; (10:27) 1980 matriculation; (11:58) Dr. Richard Schuberth's faculty address; (14:02) David Butler's calendar; (18:30) David Butler's Nightowl calendar. Speakers: Bill Bray, Norman Hackerman, Edward Kennedy, Greg Smith, Lance Crabbe, Barbara Bush, Bill Clements, Ronald Reagan, John White, David Butler, David Tuttle, Richard Schuberth
    - To the Point - Niels Nielsen, 1980-04-01; wrc06879 (Box 12)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Steve Sailer talks with Dr. Niels Nielsen about the rise of religious fundamentalism in Iran. Speakers: Niels Nielsen, Steve Sailer
    - To the Point - Walter Isle and Flournoy Manzo, 1980-04-02; wrc06880 (Box 12)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Thad Pugh talks with Dr. Walter Isle and Flournoy Manzo about "Round Two," a new college program for non-traditional students. Speakers: Walter Isle, Flournoy Manzo, Thad Pugh
    - To the Point - Paul Cloutier, 1980-04-09; wrc06881 (Box 12)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Thad Pugh talks with Dr. Paul Cloutier about mining and exploiting the space's resources. Speakers: Paul Cloutier, Thad Pugh
    - To the Point - Pat Reiff, 1980-04-11; wrc06882 (Box 12)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Mark Winstein talks with Dr. Pat Reiff about the Citizen's Environmental Coalition. Speakers: Pat Reiff, Mark Winstein
    - Men's Beer Bike race, 1980-04-12; wrc06883; 59345 (Box 12)
      Contents include: Eric Sisson and David Tuttle call the Men's Beer Bike race. Speakers: David Tuttle, Eric Sisson
    - To the Point - Carrin Dunne, 1980-04-14; wrc06884 (Box 12)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Tom Birch talks to Dr. Carrin Dunne about modern morality and concerns. Speakers: Carrin Dunne, Tom Birch
    - To the Point - Tom Hill, 1980-04-14; wrc06885 (Box 12)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Thad Pugh talks with Dr. Tom Hill about Jupiter. Speakers: Tom Hill, Thad Pugh
    - Up in the Air - Signe Walker, 1980-04-17; wrc06886; 59365 (Box 12)
      Contents include: On "Up in the Air," Suzanne Tolbert speaks with Signe Waller, widow of James Waller, M.D. who was killed by members of the Ku Klux Klan during an anti-Klan rally in Greensboro, NC on November 3, 1979. Waller is joined by a member of the Communist Worker's Party. Waller describes the event and gives background on the police's response, as well the fallout from the event. Speakers: Signe Waller, Suzanne Tolbert
    - To the Point - Ken Kennedy, 1980-04-17; wrc06887 (Box 12)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Mark Winstein talks with Dr. Ken Kennedy about the future of the computer. Speakers: Ken Kennedy, Mark Winstein
    - To the Point - Chad Gordon, 1980-04-22; wrc06888 (Box 12)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Thad Pugh talks to Dr. Chad Gordon about solar power satellites. Speakers: Chad Gordon, Thad Pugh
    - To the Point - Gilbert Cuthbertson, 1980-04-29; wrc06889 (Box 12)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Mark Winstein talks with Dr. Gilbert Cuthbertson about women in Texs history. Speakers: Gilbert Cuthbertson, Mark Winstein
    - To the Point - Gordon Wittenberg, 1980-04-30; wrc06890 (Box 12)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Mark Winstein talks with Dr. Gordon Wittenberg about energy use and architecture. Speakers: Gordon Wittenberg, Mark Winstein
    - To the Point - Bill Colson, 1980-05-08; wrc06891 (Box 12)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Thad Pugh talks to Dr. Bill Colson about free-electron lasers. Speakers: Bill Colson, Thad Pugh
    - To the Point - Meredith Skura, 1980-05-08; wrc06892 (Box 12)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Steve Sailer talks with Dr. Meredith Skura about mental illness and literature. Speakers: Meredith Skura, Steve Sailer
    - To the Point - Gordon Smith, 1980-05-30; wrc06893 (Box 12)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Thad Pugh talks with Dr. Gordon Smith about the current economic recession. Speakers: Gordon Smith, Thad Pugh
    - Richard Dobson, part 1, 1980-06-24; wrc06894_01; 59348 (Box 12)
      Contents include: Richard Dobson performs and talks about his life. We deleted radio music at end of recording. Speakers: David John Scribner, Richard Dobson
    - Richard Dobson, part 2, 1980-06-24; wrc06894_02; 59347 (Box 12)
      Contents include: Richard Dobson performs and talks about his life. We deleted radio music at the end of the recording. Speakers: David John Scribner, Richard Dobson
    - Rice Composers, 1980; wrc08005 (Box 12)
      Contents include: On "Rice Composers," Kery Jones, Scott Gehman, Rawslyn Ruffin, and Lisa Willis talk about pieces that they have composed as a brass quintet and individually. Speakers: Kerry Jones, Scott Gehman, Rawslyn Ruffin, Lisa Willis
  - Sub-Series: 1980/1981, 59342
    - To the Point - Mark Brice, 1980-07-16; wrc06962 (Box 12)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Scott Hochberg talks to Mark Brice about the documentary "Vietnam in Texas" about Seadrift, TX. Speakers: Mark Brice, Scott Hochberg
    - To the Point - Phil Bedient, 1980-07-17; wrc06963 (Box 12)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Scott Hochberg talks to Dr. Phil Bedient about drought conditions. Speakers: Phil Bedient, Scott Hochberg
    - To the Point - Robert Dix, 1980-07-17; wrc06964 (Box 12)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Scott Hochberg talks to Dr. Robert Dix about the reasons for Cuban immigration. Speakers: Robert Dix, Scott Hochberg
    - To the Point - Tom McCaleb, 1980-07-17; wrc06965 (Box 12)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Scott Hochberg talks to Dr. Tom McCaleb about problems in the auto industry. Speakers: Tom McCaleb, Scott Hochberg
    - To the Point - Frank Tittle, 1980-08-20; wrc06966 (Box 12)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Scott Hochberg talks to Dr. Frank Tittle about laser technology in China. Speakers: Frank Tittle, Scott Hochberg
    - To the Point - George Greanias, 1980-08-20; wrc06967 (Box 12)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Scott Hochberg talks to George Greanias about corporate responsibility and ethics. Speakers: George Greanias, Scott Hochberg
    - News Archive 2, 1980-08-29 - 1980-10-13; wrc06968; 59357 (Box 12)
      Contents include: (00:01) Provost William Gordon on reduction of NOTS accounts; (00:43) Lynn Lednicky on student directory; (01:09) New photo ID Cards; (02:37) Ken Dye on MOB uniforms; (02:47) Marion Hicks on Pub and Cohen House inspections; (03:02) Hally Poindexter on Dean of Humanities search; (03:14) Rice Owls football vs. Clemson preview; (04:05) Death of Dr. John Parish; (05:29) Rice Owls football vs. Tulane at Superdome; (08:34) Campanile distribution; (08:56) Dr. Stewart Baker's eulogy for Dr. John Parish; (09:22) SA senate meeting review; (10:23) Peter Rudenberg on liquor at Willy's Pub; (10:34) Rice Owls football vs. LSU and other Rice sports preview; (11:50) Daily sports report; (14:12) Rice Owls football vs. LSU review; (16:43) MOB's performance at the Rice Owls vs. LSU game; (17:59) Lovett Associate Justice resignation; (19:03) SA meeting review; (20:16) Ray Alborn on LSU win; (22:00) Mary Crisp campaigning for John B. Anderson for President; (22:31) Pres. Doris Smith announces Pres. Carter endorsement; (23:05) Farrell Gerbode on ICSA conversion of Itel AS-6 to a Model 2; (23:42) Bicycle thefts; (24:52) George H. W. Bush campaigning; (25:16) Weekend sports preview; (26:37) Rice Owls football vs. TCU review; (29:05) David Butler's calendar; (29:52) Rice Owls football vs. UT preview; (31:39) Anderson Hall renovation; (33:55) ICSA conversion to MVS; (36:38) Sid Richardson College melodrama "The Corn is Deep in Maize County" review; (39:20) Rice Owls football vs. TCU review. Speakers: William Gordon, Lynn Lednicky, Debbie Gronke, Mary Voswinkel, Ken Dye, Marion Hicks, Hally Poindexter, David Tuttle, Robin Baringer, Stewart Baker, Joe Freeland, Peter Rudenberg, Reggie Stoker, Jonathon Sadow, Nancy Burch, Reginald Stoker, David Holmes, Andy Pantos, Ray Alborn, Farrrell Gerbode, Mary Voswinkel, George H. W. Bush, Lance Crabb, O. Jack Mitchell, Jerry Stovall, Charles Rudolph, Peter Papademetriou, Priscilla Huston
    - Hemmer Ridge Mountain Boys live, 1980-09-03; wrc06969; 59362 (Box 12)
      Contents include: The Hemmer Ridge Mountain Boys perform live in Willy's Pub. We deleted dead air after the set. Speakers: Wrecks Bell, Mickey White, Michael Edwards
    - To the Point - Stephen Klineberg, 1980-09-04; wrc06970 (Box 13)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Thad Pugh talks to Dr. Stephen Klineberg about the effects of limited resources. Speakers: Stephen Klineberg, Thad Pugh
    - To the Point - Don Huddle, 1980-09-10; wrc06971 (Box 13)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Scott Hochberg talks to Dr. Don Huddle about productivity and the American worker. Speakers: Don Huddle, Scott Hochberg
    - To the Point - Robert Thrall, 1980-09-18; wrc06972 (Box 13)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Thad Pugh talks to Dr. Robert Thrall about the impact of mathematical sciences. Speakers: Robert Thrall, Thad Pugh
    - To the Point - Ewa Thompson, 1980-09-23; wrc06973 (Box 13)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Thad Pugh talks to Dr. Eva Thompson about Russia today. Speakers: Ewa Thompson, Thad Pugh
    - To the Point - Franz Brotzen, 1980-10-02; wrc06974 (Box 13)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Thad Pugh talks to Dr. Franz Brotzen about a shortage of materials, like chromium, cobalt, or manganese. Speakers: Franz Brotzen, Thad Pugh
    - To the Point - William Gordon, 1980-10-07; wrc06975 (Box 13)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Thad Pugh talks to Dr. William Gordon about Japanese technology. Speakers: William Gordon, Thad Pugh
    - To the Point - Gale Stokes, 1980-10-10; wrc06976 (Box 13)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Thad Pugh talks to Dr. Gale Stokes about turmoil in Poland. Speakers: Gale Stokes, Thad Pugh
    - News Archive 3, 1980-10-14 - 1980-11-06; wrc06977; 59358 (Box 13)
      Contents include: (00:01) Student Association meeting review; (01:03) MOB trip to Texas A and M; (01:19) Officiating in soccer games; (03:48) Objects thrown from Sid Richardson College balconies; (04:36) Sports report; (06:46) Fight at Will Rice College party; (07:49) Dr. Stewart Baker leaves Rice; (08:26) Sports report; (10:00) District #80 State Representative debate featuring Paul Colbert, Dan Downey, and Charles Fuller at Baker College; (14:19) Ron Paul and Ed Clarke speaking at Lovett College; (18:59) KTRU-Thresher political phone survey; (23:38) Weekend sports preview; (24:45) Rice Owls football vs. Arkansas review; (25:27) Weekend sports report; (27:06) Sports report; (30:01) Democratic rally at Miller Theatre; (33:03) Pres. Jimmy Carter campaign promises in 1976 analyzed; (34:42) Gene Jones headquarters; (35:48) Mike Richards headquarters; (36:49) Gene Jones on election results, Richards campaign; (38:07) Election results for Mike Richards; (39:14) Ron Paul headquarters; (39:59) Paul Colbert election results; (40:38) Paul Colbert interview; (41:19) Pres. Jimmy Carter concedes presidency; (42:08) Scott Hochberg on John Anderson headquarters; (43:21) Mike Richards voting results; (44:22) Paul Colbert plans after election; (45:12) Final Harris County returns; (46:25) Rally Club bonfire. Speakers: Joe Freeland, Ken Dye, Bruce Deskin, Jonathon Sadow, Mary Voswinkel, Bob Corrigan, Sharon Hughes, Ron Paul, Ed Clarke, David Bunch, Reginald Stocker, Paul Williams, Dave Collins, Lance Crabbe, Stewart Baker, Gary Meade, Paul Colbert, Scott Hochberg, Mike Richards, Paul Colbert, Alexis Quinlan
    - To the Point - J. Venn Leeds, 1980-10-16; wrc06978 (Box 13)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Thad Pugh talks to Dr. J. Venn Leeds about the Nuclear Regulatory Commission. Speakers: J. Venn Leeds, Thad Pugh
    - To the Point - Fred von der Mehden, 1980-10-23; wrc06979 (Box 13)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Thad Pugh talks to Dr. Fred von der Mehden about the conflicts in the Middle East. Speakers: Fred von der Mehden, Thad Pugh
    - 650 Watt Sign-on, 1980-10-28; wrc06980; 59363 (Box 13)
      Contents include: Norman Hackerman's sign-on for the new wattage, David Butler's segments recounting the history of KTRU, original skits and songs, and radio-themed songs to celebrate KTRU's increased wattage. Speakers: Norman Hackerman, David Butler
    - To the Point - Gilbert Cuthbertson, 1980-10-29; wrc06981 (Box 13)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Thad Pugh talks to Dr. Gilbert Cuthbertson about the effects of immigration on Texas politics. Speakers: Gilbert Cuthbertson, Thad Pugh
    - To the Point - Niels Nielsen, 1980-10-31; wrc06982 (Box 13)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Thad Pugh talks to Dr. Niels Nielsen about the moral majority in politics. Speakers: Niels Nielsen, Thad Pugh
    - U.S. Politics student poll, 1980-10; wrc07974 (Box 13)
      Contents include: David Bunch reports the results of a KTRU/Thresher political phone survey conducted before the 1980 presidential election. Speaker: David Bunch
    - Presidential Forum - Mock Debate, 1980-11-02; wrc06983; 59361 (Box 13)
      Contents include: "Presidential Forum" simulates a presidential debate with stand-ins for the candidates, Scott Hochberg for the John B. Anderson campaign, Dan O'Meara [sp?] for the Ronald Reagan campaign, Peter Elloway for the Clark campaign, and Barbara Stanley for the Pres. Jimmy Carter campaign. We deleted radio music at the end of the recording. Speakers: David Bunch, Richard Dees, Gilbert Cuthbertson, Scott Hochberg, Peter Elloway, Barbara Stanley
    - News Telescope Election Night, 1980-11-04; wrc06984; 59355 (Box 13)
      Contents include: Coverage of the 1980 election night both local and national. Dr. David Gow provides analysis. We have deleted radio music and fixed the speed at the end of the tape. Speakers: David Tuttle, David Bunch, David Gow, Gary Meade, Jimmy Carter, Dave Collins, Paul Colbert, Gene Jones, Mike Richards
    - News Archive 4, 1980-11-07 - 1981-02-16; wrc06985; 59359 (Box 13)
      Contents include: (00:01) Chapel services for Rice Owls football team; (02:10) Abercrombie Lab expansion; (04:45) Rice Owls football vs. SMU preview; (08:42) Rice's Quarterback Club meeting and pro games; (10:29) Family style dining; (11:31) Willy's Pub rent to Rice Memorial Center; (12:36) John "Grungy" Gladu on Baylor Bunny Show and Playboy magazine's coverage; (14:16) Sports reports; (20:27) Rice Players' "Caucasian Chalk Circle" review; (23:02) Weekend sports preview; (24:28) Weekend sports review; (26:15) Willy's Pub closing in summer; (28:30) SA schedule poll; (29:09) Student directories late; (30:40) Change to schedule; (31:11) No replacement for SA External VP; (31:37) Student directory delayed; (32:22) SA news; (33:51) Pres. Ronald Reagan's oath of office; (34:43) Policy Studies major; (35:51) Phi Beta Kappa fall contingent; (37:08) New ICSA building; (37:57) Wiess College votes against going co-ed; (40:19) Lynn Ashby speaks at Rice; (42:33) Rice Players' "What the Butler Saw" review; (44:32) TexPIRG possible dissolution; (45:30) Texas law to raise drinking age to 19. Speakers: Dave Chilton, Larry Allen, Hardie Bourland, Reginald Stoker, Randy Hertel, Jonathan Sadow, Gary Meade, Marion Hicks, Peter Rudenberg, John "Grungy" Gladu, David Bunch, Ed Holt, Tim Stout, Lynn Lednicky, Bill Brey, Debbie Gronke, Warren Burger, Dave Collins, Carl McDowell, Lynn Ashby
    - To the Point - Pat Reiff, 1980-11-12; wrc06986 (Box 13)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Thad Pugh talks to Dr. Pat Reiff about the sun. Speakers: Pat Reiff, Thad Pugh
    - To the Point - Tom Hill, 1980-11-20; wrc06987 (Box 13)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Thad Pugh talks to Dr. Tom Hill about new data about Saturn. Speakers: Tom Hill, Thad Pugh
    - To the Point - Joseph Short, 1980-12-03; wrc06988 (Box 13)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Thad Pugh talks to Dr. Joseph Short, Director of Oxfam America, about world hunger. Speakers: Joseph Short, Thad Pugh